<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AesopsFables</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assandthe_lapdog">TheAssandtheLapdog</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_asss_brains">TheAsssBrains</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assandthe_charger">TheAssandtheCharger</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assinthe_lions_skin">TheAssintheLionsSkin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_androcles">Androcles</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_old_hound">TheOldHound</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_mischievous_dog">TheMischievousDog</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_lionin_love">TheLioninLove</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_cat_maiden">TheCatMaiden</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bellingthe_cat">BellingtheCat</string>
    <string name="fable_8_text">A Lion once fell in love with a beautiful maiden and proposed marriage to her parents.\n

The old people did not know what to say.\n

They did not like to give their daughter to the Lion, yet they did not wish to enrage the King of Beasts.\n

At last the father said:

"We feel highly honoured by your Majesty\'s proposal, but you see our daughter is a tender young thing, and we fear that in the vehemence of your affection you might possibly do her some injury. Might I venture to suggest that your Majesty should have your claws removed, and your teeth extracted, then we would gladly consider your proposal again."

The Lion was so much in love that he had his claws trimmed and his big teeth taken out.\n

But when he came again to the parents of the young girl they simply laughed in his face, and bade him do his worst.\n
    </string>

    <string name="fable_1_text">A Farmer one day came to the stables to see to his beasts of burden: among them was his favourite Ass, that was always well fed and often carried his master.

With the Farmer came his Lapdog, who danced about and licked his hand and frisked about as happy as could be./n

The Farmer felt in his pocket, gave the Lapdog some dainty food, and sat down while he gave his orders to his servants.

The Lapdog jumped into his master\'s lap,and lay there blinking while the Farmer stroked his ears.\n

The Ass, seeing this, broke loose from his halter and commenced prancing about in imitation of the Lapdog.

The Farmer could not hold his sides with laughter, so the Ass went up to him, and putting his feet upon the Farmer\'s shoulder attempted to climb into his lap.\n

The Farmer\'s servants rushed up with sticks and pitchforks and soon taught the Ass that: Clumsy jesting is no joke.



 </string>



</resources>
